No way! I refuse to accept that!
I don't understand.
Accept it or not, I am Ken Takakura.
Stop it!
I don't wanna hear it!
Crap! The curse!
Miss Ayase! Hurry!
Your psychic powers!
Lemme gobble that weenie!
Th-Thank you very much.
Let's set a few rules.
No speaking your name.
Okay.
Because you like the occult, you're Okarun.
O-Okarun.
If you use that name, I'll kill you.
"That name"? It's my own name.
Well, I guess I have no choice,
so that's fine.
You don't seem that upset about it,
Okarun!
What? This is against my will!
Hey, lemme see your face!
You're looking happy, Okarun!
Stinky!
You farted in front of my face!
You're the worst!
It's because you're
putting pressure on me, Miss Ayase!
Hold on a sec! It's already morning!
That means Turbo Granny
won't come out anymore?
Huh? Is that true?
I mean, ghosts show up at night, right?
Why don't you come to my place for now?
That outfit...
is scarier than a ghost.
EPISODE 2
THAT'S A SPACE ALIEN,
AIN'T IT?!
My Grandma's really hard on guys,
so be careful.
She almost killed a previous boyfriend.
Huh? You wait till now to say that?
What's going on?
Okarun! Are you okay?
Must be this.
PEACEFUL PROSPEROUS FAMILY
WARD AGAINST EVIL AND MISFORTUNE
Sorry, Okarun!
A barrier's been put up!
I thought I was gonna die.
Okay, now try coming in!
Is it really gonna be okay?
If you burn, I'll toss you
into the river again, so it's okay.
Whoa. Freaky.
You're safe!
How do you feel?
Any changes?
My entire body tingles.
More like, what's with your head?
Totally hilarious! It's a granny perm!
Freaky! What are you laughing about?
I was about to die there!
Grandma!
Huh? Grandma's not here.
Oh well. Come on up.
E-Excuse me.
Hold on a minute.
I'll change clothes, so close the door.
Oh, okay.
Miss Ayase! The curse!
Hey! Don't just open the door!
Face the wall!
STAY OUT
I-I'm sorry.
Sheesh, what a pain.
Okarun, put these on.
It's ladieswear but it should be okay.
Sorry to trouble you.
By the way, you don't have
anything down there, do you?
What? What do you mean?
I'm sorry! I didn't look!
It's fine now.
Hey, hey.
Show me what's down there.
Turbo Granny was saying that you're cursed
because your weenie has been taken.
It's gone!
What? No way!
What's it look like? Show me!
I can't show you! Are you stupid?
But there's nothing there, right?
The issue isn't whether or not it's there!
Man, you're so cheap.
This is the worst!
What are we gonna do about this?
It's not there!
Don't make it sound like I'm the villain.
You're the one who challenged me!
Huh?
I wasn't interested
in your occult stories to begin with!
I only picked a fight
because you kept talking to me!
I didn't want to miss my chance.
I've always wanted a friend.
So I thought,
I didn't want to miss this chance.
That's why I so desperately
started talking to you.
But in the end...
You live in a different world, Miss Ayase.
You're not someone that a person like me
should be talking to.
I'm so sorry...
that I roped you into so much danger.
When this is all over,
you can just ignore me again.
That's the annoying part about you.
You assume how others feel
and jump to conclusions without asking.
The reason you don't have friends
is because you shove them away.
Don't say that I can ignore you.
We can just talk about
the occult like normal.
Hey, say something.
Poke, poke.
You're so ugly!
Huh?
What did you just say, punk?
You are completely tactless, Miss Ayase!
You bluntly recite people's weaknesses!
What the hell is tact?
Perhaps your grandmother is back?
Shh! Stay quiet.
I've never heard a doorbell like this.
What do you mean?
Grandma told me in the past...
that we have two doorbells.
One is for humans,
and the other is for...
evil spirits.
Crap! It's because I took that talisman off!
It's okay if it's for a little bit, right?
Oh, no!
There's something out there!
What are we gonna do?
I'll put the talisman back up!
If it's an evil spirit,
it'll burn up like you did, right?
Are you going to burn me, too?
You can just get outside of our plot!
Please wait to put up the talisman
until I step outside!
It's gone. Where did it go?
Miss Ayase! Look at this!
Crap! Crap!
We gotta leave the plot now!
Go that way! Hurry!
- Miss Ayase!
- What!?
We can't get out.
We're trapped inside by a wall.
The torii gate!
I can attach the talisman!
Please wait!
You can't put the talisman up!
Why not?
The torii gate is embedded into the wall!
We can't leave the plot like this!
What should we do?
If we don't do anything, we're seriously...
What is this?
We're in serious trouble!
Miss Ayase!
Help... me...
Okarun, are you okay?
Get a grip on yourself!
Blood!
Black fog. So it's because of that.
Found... you...
You are evil people.
You broke the promise.
Give me...
your banana organ!
Crap! What's with that evil spirit?
Wait, you have another one down there?
Of course not!
That's an alien!
Huh?
There's no doubt about it! That collar!
That's a Flatwoods Monster!
They were first witnessed in a town
in America called Flatwoods.
In Japan, they've been sighted in Yamanashi.
They're known as aliens
who are three meters tall.
Then what was that doorbell?
You're saying a chime specifically for ghosts
reacted to an alien?
There are studies that say people who see
spiritual phenomena often see UFOs as well!
In other words, there might be something
in common between ghosts and aliens!
Is that a buddy of the aliens
from yesterday? They're so persistent!
If we don't hurry up and do something
about that thing, the poison fog will kill us!
But if I'm holding Okarun's curse back,
I can't use my psychic powers well.
Miss Ayase.
Sheesh, what a pain!
Huh?
Sheesh!
Miss Ayase.
What is it now?
I will fight.
Please release the curse!
What's this so suddenly?
I'm not afraid of aliens!
Can you release just the physical curse
while keeping my head in check?
You make it sound easy, but I haven't learned
how to control this power!
If all goes well, we might be able
to control that Granny's powers!
I'm not sure if I can do it right!
Please try!
- Miss Ayase! Here it comes!
- Give it to me!
Please hurry!
This is amazing.
I'm brimming with power!
But I'm totally depressed.
Whoa! Is his psyche broken?
My conscious is clear, yo...
But I totally have the blues, yo...
What's with that manner of speech?
Oh, sorry.
I am an awkward fellow after all, yo...
I told you not to say that!
I should just, yo...
Eradicate myself, yo?
Stop talking like that! It pisses me off!
I'll be back in a little bit.
I'm sure it won't work, yo...
Hey!
Look ahead! In front of you!
My body moved outta reflex.
So this is Turbo Granny's powers?
I feel so dejected.
So fast. When'd he learn to do that?
This is amazing! Maybe we can do this!
Wait, what's going on?
Okarun!
Give it to me!
Crap!
Okarun, are you okay?
I'm sorry, Miss Ayase!
My body can't keep up
with the power of the curse!
My entire body feels like
it's going to burst into a million pieces!
This isn't a speed that humans can move in!
But I've only damaged
five fingers from that thing!
How the hell are we gonna defeat
something like that?
Like I know! Don't get pissed at me!
If we knew how to defeat it,
we wouldn't be struggling!
That thing...
Is it sumo wrestling?
Come again?
If we can get its hand
to touch the ground, maybe we win?
Miss Ayase, are you a genius?
I knew I was.
Next time is my limit, okay?
Okarun, aim for the legs.
I'll make the thing trip
with my psychic powers!
Man, I'm so depressed.
We have to get a bit closer,
so you have to back me up!
What a pain.
Give me your banana!
I can't take it anymore!
Hold back the curse with my right hand,
and I'll take on this guy with my left hand!
What a pain!
Oh, hold on.
Sorry, Okarun!
All right! The hand is melting!
Just like how we planned!
You're kidding.
Miss Ayase, run for it!
Miss Ayase!
Crap. This is bad news.
I'm back.
Sheesh. You really are a nuisance.
Hey, sumo alien!
You put your hand on the ground.
That's cheating, you scumbag.
Miss Ayase!
Please release the curse one more time!
I don't care what happens to my body!
I'm gonna beat the crap outta this thing!
You sit and watch, Okarun!
I can't let cheaters off the hook!
Wait, what are you saying?
You really pissed me off, wimpy alien.
Stop it!
That did nothing!
Please release my curse, Miss Ayase!
I'm begging you!
If this keeps up, you'll die!
This is fine.
This depth is great.
Because if I'm in this deep...
it means I'm outside of the torii gate!
PEACEFUL PROSPEROUS FAMILY
WARD AGAINST EVIL AND MISFORTUNE
We're back.
We're saved.
Okarun! We're back! See?
Oh, yes.
I really thought I was gonna die!
Oh! Miss Ayase, the curse!
Come on! Don't be a pain!
At least let me indulge in the moment!
You say that, but I can't
do anything about this.
What? You change your hairdo?
Of course not!
That kinda looks good.
I did prefer the granny perm, though.
But you made fun of it!
Huh? I'm kinda dizzy.
Oh, crap.
Huh?
Miss Ayase?
Get a hold of yourself! Miss Ayase!
In 1952, several boys and soldiers, as well as
their pet dog, encountered the Flatwoods Monster.
The granny perm
was better on you after all.
Back in those days, the local residents...
Are you listening to my story?
EPISODE 3
IT'S A GRANNY VS. GRANNY CLASH!
Next episode:
"It's a Granny vs. Granny Clash!"
They're called "aliens who are
three meters tall" in Japan.